Signe K. Kiil

27-01-1988

T: +610479106557 E: signekkiil@gmail.com

About me

I am a 30 year old woman originally from Denmark. Last year I travelled Canada on a working holiday visa. I now live in Melbourne, on a working holiday visa for 1 year. I love to travel and experience new things, and have been fortunate enough to be able to do so. I love working with children and young people, I find it very rewarding. I have obtained my working with children check here in Australia, and I am waiting for my Danish teaching degree to be recognized by the Victorian government so I can work as a teacher. In the meantime I am working as a teachers assistant.

Experience

Kop&Kande (Danish interior design/cookware store)

August 2008 - August 2014

I worked here 2 years full time, and then 4 years part time while studying for my bachelors degree. I worked as a sales assistant and therefore have a lot of experience with sales and customer service. After being employed for a year I was given more responsibilities which I kept while being part time as well. I was in charge of ordering goods, making new time sheets, training new staff and opening and closing the store.

Søgårdhus skole

August 2013 - August 2014

I worked part time as an ESL teacher at an institution for criminal youth while I was still finishing my degree. I taught 5 boys aged 15-17, that for various reasons were no longer in public school, and had never finished their exams. I was responsible for their oral exam at the end of the year which they all passed.

Vedbæk skole

August 2014 - August 2016

After I finished my bachelors degree I worked, full time for 2 years, as a middle school (4th - 6th grade/ 10-13 year olds) teacher. I taught English as a second language, biology, social studies, history and religion. I did one year as the head teacher of a 4th grade. That included having main responsibilities for the children's well-being with weekly "class-meetings". I also was the main school/home communicator with weekly and monthly updates for the parents. I resigned this positions to travel Canada.

Rasmussen family

August 2017 - December

I worked as a private teacher for a family that had taken their son out of school to travel. Together we went to France, Italy, Malta, Costa Rica and Mexico. I taught the son in all subjects of 6th grade from the Danish curriculum. I resigned this position to move to Australia.

Education

Bachelor of Education

August 2010 - August 2014

I took my Bachelor of Education at Copenhagen at University College Copenhagen (Zahle's lærerseminarium). I am educated to teach English as a second language, Biology and Social Studies.

Besides the subjects you choose, all teachers in Denmark must study psychology, KLM (formation and culture) and pedagogy and didactics.

Qualifications

I have a lot of experience with sales and customer service through my job at the interior design store. I love working with people, and see myself as a "people's person".

From my teaching job, and education, I have excellent language skills, and a lot of experience with problem solving. Furthermore it made me a champ of multitasking, all while having a great deal of patience.

Teaching also naturally gave me great leadership skills.

I have a lot of different experience in working with children. I worked with troubled, criminal youth. I worked in a "normal" classroom in different age groups. I worked as a private teacher, so I have one on one teaching experience as well.

I very much look forward to hearing from you.

Kind regards, Signe Kleemeyer Kiil